[{"answer": "Yeah, yeah, so...gi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Well, if I didn't do something I wouldn't be able to live with myself", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Still a 31 waist", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, you should admire me...I'm aspiring to date a giving person", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "That's why I should date a giving person. If I date a taking person, everyone's taking, taking, taking, no one's giving", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I got a date with that girl, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I actually met her a few weeks ago, but...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, how'd you meet her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You met her a few weeks ago, but...", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Guess who volunteered last week", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, o.k., yeah. Where am I gonna park here...?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Me run in? Why don't you run in", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You don't know what I use for birth control, do you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You do? What", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's a poker game... And I'm kickin' some serious butt", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, you gotta be kiddin'! You see those two ladies I got showin'? Do they look scared?", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well...my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend loves the sponge", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How'd you find out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Really? How'd she do that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "My my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You're cutting me off? No, no, no my friend, don't cut me off", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Too good..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hey, I didn't even use one", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, it was, but then I just couldn't decide if he was really spong", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I have to", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't wear the ribbon", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah, I'm against AIDS. I mean, I'm walking, aren't I? I just don't wear the ribbon", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, we've gone out several times, we obviously have a good rapport. I own a very profitable electronics distributing firm. I eat well. I exercise. Blood tests", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah, I told you...I'm going to trim my sideburns", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I can see that. What do you have to do that for? Who cares about your pants size", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'd kill to be a 32", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't wanna be a 32", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "She said I wasn't spong", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No regrets", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Nope.  What are you doing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sponge.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Oh...I don't think so", "qsentId": 44}]